brickworkindia.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction:

Brickwork India is a global leader in providing Remote Executive Assistance (herein after "Remote EA Services") to organizations worldwide. We provide customized and personalized Remote EA services under admin, knowledge and technical portfolio.

We understand our customer's unique needs and has crafted specialized services. Customers use our services in several ways to manage their non-core/routine tasks to become more productive by re-purposing their time.

We recognize that, you provide us with information about yourself to provide services that you request and you trust us to act in a responsible manner as per applicable laws.

We strongly advocate the protection of our customers' privacy and to ensure that their personal and/or company information is safeguarded. We have adopted aggressive policies that outline Brickwork's privacy principles and it is our belief that they effectively capture our commitment to you.

This privacy policy helps you to understand what we information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can update, manage and delete the information.

You acknowledge that your continued use of our services after we publish or send a notice about our changes to this Privacy Policy means that the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to the updated Privacy Policy.

## Applicability:

This policy applies to any natural or legal person who intend to use our services. This privacy policy applies to Brickworkindia.com, Brickwork branded apps, SlideShare, Apps, Communication and services including onsite services and ad services.

## Data Controllers:

If you reside in "EU counties", you will be the data controller of your personal data provided to us for processing activities relating to the services you have selected; you are entering the Terms of Services with Brickwork India.

As a visitor or user of our services, the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to this privacy policy and updates.

## What personal information are collected:

You provide the below listed personal data to create an account with us to utilize our services.

The information includes unique identifiers first name, last name, job title, company name, website, country, email, phone, Zip code, credit card number, passport number, social security number. We also collect your IP address, referrer name, email id, your food preference, flight preference to provide the service.

If you become a customer, you will provide payment (e.g., credit card) and billing information.

Personal Information does not include aggregated information that, by itself, does not permit the identification of individual persons (like statistics relating to the number of person visiting our web site for the previous week or month and alike). It may also include other information when needed to provide a service you request and the same is used in accordance with applicable laws. 

## Why the personal information are collected:

We collect and use only such information as is needed for legitimate business purposes and as may be permitted in the applicable jurisdictions.

We collect the personal information, when you:

(a) register to use the services, (b) complete survey questionnaires, and send e-mail messages, submit forms or send other information to us.

We may collect your personal information with your consent at various stages of project execution by clearly stating the purpose.

## How we collect the information:

We do not collect any personal data without your consent. We have not enabled "cookies" to in our website to keep track of information you provide during a single browser session.

In the web forms enabled in our website (Request for Information and Quick Submit), we collect information about yourself, the service you prefer, acceptance to our terms of services and consent to use your personal data. The web form details are stored in Go daddy server, website database, our intranet database and in Salesforce.

During the project execution, depends on the service you have requested, we may collect other required personal data.

In the payment link, you enter your credit card information to process the payment. This information is not stored in our website or databases. The payment requests are processed by a third party "Authorize.net" or Axis Bank.

## Activity information:

We collect information about your activity while using our services, to provide personalized service like booking your preferred seat in the flight, ordering your favourite food. The activity information we collect may include:

If you use our service to make and receive calls, calendar management, meeting arrangement, email management, we may collect your phone number, calling party-number, receiving-party number, time and date of the call, meeting, duration of the meeting, access to your calendar, access to your mail box.

## Location information:

We collect information about your location, IP address, to allocate suitable Remote EA, align their shift timings and for future business meet.

We also collect information about you from publicly accessible sources. For e.g., we use LinkedIn to collect the information about your business, to understand your business and recommend the suitable service offered by us and to share relevant case studies of your industry.

## How we use your data

We use your personal information to deliver the services that are tailored specifically to your requirement and to improve the services that you request from us.

We use the collected information for the following purposes:

## Communication:

We use the information we collect, like your email address, phone number, to interact with you directly on a regular basis. For example, the Remote EA will be sending a task deliverable or project report daily to your email id.

## Provide Remote EA services:

We use your information to provide the services you have opted for. For e.g., if you sync your contacts or calendars with our services, we will access your address book and calendar meeting information to schedule meetings or setting reminders for you and others, and by providing information about them, e.g. times, places, attendees and contacts.

## Personalized Service:

We provide some personalized services based on your interests. You can control what information we use to provide personalized service to you unless you ask us to share the information on your behalf. For example, if you request us to order food from the restaurants, using your credit card information.

## Maintain & improve our services:

We also use your information to provide the service as per your expectation, such as tracking your feedbacks, resolving the escalations you have raised with us and to contact you regarding the services which may be of interest to you. We use information to improve our services - for example, understanding which meeting room you prefer for your meetings and check the availability of the same.

## Develop new service:

We use the information we collected to provide customized service including providing recommendations. For example, if you are using the multiple excel reports for decision making, create an automated dashboard to save your time and effort in referring multiple reports.

## Direct Marketing:

Currently, we don't share your personal information with any marketing companies, advertising agencies without your permission.

## Related Companies and Other Services:

We receive data about you when you use some of the other services provided by our affiliates, including Microsoft. For example, we use Outlook, for exchanging emails with you.

## Measure performance:

You can prefer to browse most pages of our site without identifying yourself or revealing any information about you or your company. We may collect, retain and use certain non-personal information for tracking our visitors to determine section of our website which attract your interest, the nature of content accessed and how long you were browsing our site.

We use Google analytics, to analyse your visit to our website to improve our website design and navigations. This information is used to perform routine website maintenance and to generate aggregate web site traffic reports so we can develop site content and features of value to you and to provide general statistics regarding use of BrickworkIndia.com.

We use feedback form, to know your feedback on the services offered.

## Service Providers:

We use others to help us provide our Services (e.g., maintenance, analysis, audit, payments, fraud detection, marketing and development). They will have access to your information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for other purposes.

## Data Disclosure:

We have implemented security measures, which guard access to and disclosure of information.

Brickwork disclose your personal information to individuals who work on behalf of or with Brickwork under strict confidentiality agreements solely in the legitimate conduct of business to deliver services and to provide special offers designed to meet your requirements.

They will have access to your information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for other purposes. However, these individuals do not have any independent right to further share or disseminate this information.

Brickwork does not sell, trade, permit usage or rent your personal information to any third party without your consent. No disclosure of personally identifiable information is made to third parties unless there is an appropriate legal or business justification. Outsourced contract with a third- party company to perform specific services that require us to provide access to customer information will be in adherence to the same confidentiality policies effective with Brickwork.

Brickwork may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, this information when disclosed is in aggregate form and does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. Continued internal audits performed will ensure that we are complying within the policies in place to protect our customers.

## Legal Disclosures:

We may also use your data (including your communications) if we think it's necessary for security purposes or to investigate possible fraud or other violations of our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy and/or attempts to harm our Members or Visitors.

Brickwork may also release information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (2) enforce or apply terms of the Brickwork's Web site user agreement; or (3) protect the rights, property or safety of Brickwork or others.; (4) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; or (5) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations.

## Data Retention:

As per our data retention policy, we retain your personal data for 10 years or if it is needed to provide you Services. This includes data you or others provided to us and data generated or inferred from your use of our services and from publicly accessible sources. Even if you only use our services for a shorter period, we will retain your information and keep your account active until you decide to close. In some cases, we choose to retain certain information (e.g., your project information) in a depersonalized or aggregated form.

## Your rights & obligations:

You can request us to modify or delete your personal data. Soon, you will be able to access your personal data through tools.

## Data Accuracy:

We maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us. You can ask us to change, update or fix your data if it's inaccurate. Soon, we will allow you to review and update your information directly.

## Restriction on usage:

You can ask us to stop using all or some of your personal data (e.g., if we have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if your personal data is inaccurate or unlawfully held).

## Data Erasure:

You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data (e.g., if it is no longer necessary to provide Services to you).

## Data Portability:

You can ask us for a copy of your personal data and can ask for a copy of personal data you provided in machine readable form. You can contact us using the contact information given below, and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.

## Data Security:

BrickworkIndia.com maintains security procedures to help prevent unauthorized access to confidential information. We work hard to protect your information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold including:

  * We take reasonable steps to ensure that all dealings with personal information shall be processed fairly and lawfully and shall be kept secure against unauthorized or unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage, as per the prescribed standards.
  * We regularly monitor our system for possible vulnerabilities and security breaches.
  * We update and test our technology to assure the integrity of our systems and to improve upon our existing privacy safeguards wherever possible.
  * We use encryption to keep your data private while in transit.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to prevent unauthorized access to our system.
  * We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents, who need that information to process it or to provide you the services. Anyone with this access is subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Consent:

We have enabled the consent form in our web forms for collection and use of your personal information for legitimate business purpose. As Brickwork operates globally, your information may be stored and processed in or any other country in which Brickwork or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

## Legitimate Processing:

We will only collect and process your personal data on lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you (e.g. to deliver the Brickwork Services you have requested)) and "legitimate interests".

Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time by writing an email to [privacy@brickworkIndia.com.](mailto:privacy@brickworkIndia.com.) where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the right to object. If you have any questions about the lawful bases upon which we collect and use your personal data, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@brickworkIndia.com.](mailto:privacy@brickworkIndia.com.)

## Account Closure:

If you choose to close your account, your personal data will be archived and made invisible within 72 hours.

We retain your personal data even after you have closed your account if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our User Agreement, or fulfil your request to "unsubscribe" from further messages from us. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed.

## Cross-Border Data Transfers:

We process, store and use your data in India and may have laws which are different, and potentially not as protective, as the laws of your own country.

## Policy Subject to Change:

Brickwork reserves the right to change its privacy policies and procedures and will post changes on this page. It is our commitment to keep you informed when changes and type of data is collected; it's usage and third-party disclosure. Please check this page for changes from time to time to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices. If you object to any changes, you may request to close your association with us.

## Contact BrickworkIndia.com

We are committed to protecting your privacy. If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@brickworkIndia.com.](mailto:privacy@brickworkIndia.com.)

We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. Thank you for your support of these policies and of BrickworkIndia.com or use of these websites.
